all pirates searching for the treasure one piece must brave the second half of the grand line
these wild and dangerous seas are known as the new world the old roger and his crew were the
only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held for the rest of the
pirates of the world this has proven to be the end of the road a graveyard of dreams
now monkey d luffy a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit
set sail into the new world with his faithful crew i'm gonna be the king of the pirates
two years have passed since the war of the best in marineford reuniting after this special training
luffy and his crew continue on to the new world their first stop is fishman island thousands of
feet below sea level where trouble seems to find them wherever they go the fishman pirates led by
hordy jones plot to overthrow king neptune and rule the kingdom they have teamed up with vander deccan
who has eyes on the mermaid princess it's a pleasure mr hordy jones the straw hat pirates who had hoped to
leave the island have now become entrenched in its conflict
but isn't there someplace that you want to go
well of course there is there are lots of places that i'd love to see why thought you'd say that
what so let's get out of here if that guy throws something at you fine i'll take it down just like
the last time
it's quite formidable
Zoro hold on i thought they locked you up sounded like you guys were having some fun so here i am
it's an emergency the ryugu palace is occupied
oh no
how did he escape from his jail cell so quickly
i can't believe a human could deflect an attack from the mighty king neptune he's no ordinary pirate
my word if you resist both sides will undoubtedly suffer casualties it would be noble for you to
surrender zori it's zoro don't just stand there rupture the bubble around them at once what for
because we fish men will obviously have the advantage when it comes to nautical combat now strike
well this does not look good for us we need to come up with a plan fast hear that nami
she's gone
huh what's happening
oh no the water they drained it from the room
sorry about that i couldn't help myself once i saw this big piece of bubbly coral
holy crap that thing's huge all right then what do you say we finish what we started
uh fine lower your weapon i will fight him myself no sire i cannot allow you to engage in such barbaric
acts whether you can allow it or not matters little these opponents are strong and i refuse to let
anyone else get hurt
so are you gonna get ready or not we're wasting time let's go wait uh you want us to leave right now
but i mean this is happening so fast i need to think what's there to think about well
i've never done anything like this so i'm nervous i haven't been outside in so long
can you give me a moment to decide we're just talking about going for a walk it's no big deal
sure you can have a minute but only a minute because i don't like you
oh no what have you guys done yeah this is overkill they're not bad guys they were just doing
their jobs you didn't have to be so rough in case you forgot it was you guys who started this fight
all i did was save you idiots we would have been fine if we just acted tough and then ran for it
to think i gave up sightseeing and shopping on the island to come here what's the point of even
complaining about it anyway not like we could take it back the point is it shouldn't have happened
we look like villains now no one's gonna believe we took a trip to fish man island and just happened
to seize their palace would you prefer we let ourselves get captured i'd prefer if we gone with my
run away plan like i said which wouldn't have worked because i don't know how to get out of
here and luffy's still missing that's a really good point that i hadn't thought about any idea where
luffy went no we really have to go so could you help us out pretty please maybe he can tell you
where to find luffy tell me where i can find the treasure vault cut it out who me don't play innocent
with me you think i don't know how your greedy brain works all right everybody let's take a little
break and turn those frowns upside down with rock it'll be all right no reason to fight words of
mine aren't lies everybody dies you aren't helping the situation soaking are you feeling any better now
your highness i can't believe that even the great knight of the sea was bested by these mongrels
things would have been different if i hadn't thrown my back out all of a sudden
i don't know when i became so old this is all my fault forgive me don't say that your highness
if we had gathered our wit sooner we could have burst their bubbles in one easily now that they've
drained the water from the room it's hopeless and who will rescue us now hey you criminals it's only
a matter of time before nepcune's sons fukaboshi ryoboshi and manboshi return to the palace and once
they get here you're all going to be sorry doesn't matter who's coming we have to make it off this
island our first step should be getting everyone together then we find the sunny and get the hell
out of here but we lost our coding when we got here so even if we knew where it was we couldn't
escape on it as it is to top it all off the log pose hasn't been working it's been going haywire
ever since we arrived on the island you can't be serious if you believe a primitive pose like that
will get you through the new world then you're even dumber than you look wait are you trying to
say that my gear isn't good enough i'm not saying anything unless you untie me first
ding dong ding it must be prince fukaboshi it's time this is quite unusual what could be delaying the
guards from answering who's this what do you want ah what are you doing hang up prince fukaboshi
everybody shut up prince ryoboshi prince manboshi oh no something's wrong i can hear them call for
me it sounds like they're in trouble but i didn't hear father shirihoshi it's us the three princes what
has happened with whom am i currently speaking open the gate and grant us passage that is an order
from the royal family wow i'm really shaking in my boots here sorry you're not coming in okay how
about we just hang up you don't need to make them angry can you do kami and me a favor and tie us up
so we don't look like your accomplices saro chen is scary get us out of here
so tell me are you a member of the straw hat pirates he is my son the man you are speaking
to is their green-haired swordsman pirate hunter zori that's father is he all right yeah he's alive
well for now anyway but if you want him and the others to stay like that you're gonna have to run
some errands for us you can start by getting us ready to sail out of here what that means is finding
our ship the sunny and getting a fresh new coating slapped on it and i mean finding because we got no
clue where it is right now while you're at it round up our crew we're missing a gloomy lady a big robot
thing talking raccoon and a little goblin pervert and demands one million berries and unmarked cash you
stop spurring him on fine i accept your conditions i will make the proper arrangements
for you and your friends to leave fish man island you have my word however i will dismiss our contract
if any of the hostages are harmed it's a deal but brother we have no choice but to agree as you are
aware this gateway is the only means of entering ryugu palace even for us of the royal family
while we could try to gain access from another area there is simply no way for us to penetrate
the layers of bubbles there's something i must say before we go i wouldn't normally share this
information given the circumstances however i am honor bound to deliver the message regardless
i'm listening they are from the first son of the sea and former warlord jimbae for straw hat luffy
these were meant to be delivered upon your arrival on the island as part of your welcoming but here we
are jimbae but why and how do they know jimbae wait that's right yeah luffy said jimbae was his friend
true the two of them even appeared together in the newspaper a while back despite being a pirate jimbae is
almost like a hero to the people down here unfortunately luffy isn't with us right at this moment but i'll
pass the messages on go you would have my thanks the first is do not fight hordi and as for the second
jimbae will wait in the sea forest that is all
don't fight hordi what does that even mean
hence our situation as a result you are hereby ordered to locate the straw hat ship and remaining
crew members as quickly as possible we understand sire it will be done sire you can count on us sire
have you heard the rumors going around the ones about the straw hat pirates it's crazy you think
they really took over yugu palace what is it they're after anyway that can't be i met them
they seem like such nice people i can't believe they do such a thing i can't believe they do that
can't believe they do that i can believe they do that maybe i can't believe it either who cares if i
can't believe it i bet they did kidnap those mermaids and the way things are going it won't be long before
they come after the rest of us madam charlie's vision is coming true i guess they're finally showing
their true colors i heard that two of them have been hiding around here in the back of the mermaid
cafe that's why the guards are inspecting it right now what the hell what is that thing
the animal transformed it's time for kung fu point sanji's finally recovering he needs peace and
quiet at any cost you want to take us to the ryugu palace huh i don't know what's happening here but
we're not going hey chopper you okay sanji you shouldn't be up and about
i'm sorry i can't though i'd like to then why not you said there was somewhere you wanted to see
didn't you i did but if i leave my room it'll cause a lot of problems and not just for me but for
everyone in the palace too look i'm not telling you how to live your life but i'd be going crazy if
i was stuck in one room for 10 years i'll make sure you're safe it's my thanks for all that food so
where do you want to go
the sea the sea forest
sorry i suppose it's a foolish dream i could never forgive myself for doing something so selfish
just forget about it we're just standing here talking what are you apologizing for because i can't
stop crying just saying that took all of my courage please don't get angry and start yelling at me again
it's really frightening when you do that such a pain in the butt the hell what's all that noise
he's not throwing axes again is he this guy's got real issues
that doesn't sound good no why now of all times vander deccan must be behind this he's attacking the
hard shell tower shira hoshi is in danger tell me how many guards are with her unfortunately all of the
guards are tied up here sire listen pirates i need you to go check on the princess this is an emergency
whoa we have to do what now no king neptune we can't possibly trust them with her safety
i'm afraid there simply isn't any other choice the hard shell tower is on the northeast side of the
palace please you have to hurry there immediately do you not realize that as a hostage you don't
get to make demands be quiet you shira hoshi is the only daughter i have you may not realize but
her life is constantly under threat if anything should happen to her while you occupy our home i will send
you all to your graves at the bottom of an ocean tricks how could i possibly refuse going to her
rescue i shall rush to her aid in this her greatest moment of need completely selflessly of course no
hint of an ulterior motive although if she wanted to show me her panties that would be fine wait brook
it might be a trap no this is awful the only one of them who's willing to help us has the most
and pure of intentions she is in worst danger now that ever please take me with you you don't have
to untie me but i insist that i accompany you skeleton the tower is my jurisdiction if anything happens
to the princess i will never be able to overcome my shame
i understand your desire to see panties too i would never this is calandra it's not true
i can't be sorry to burden you but it truly is my dream to go to the sea forest
and these 10 years i couldn't whenever i talk about making the trip everyone goes out of their
way to tell me how dangerous it would be for me to leave so i've never pushed the issue because i'm too
afraid tell me the truth are you really willing to take me to the sea forest despite the trouble
you'll face yes and you promise to protect me no matter what happens right of course i will count on me
whoa hold on i'm not gonna do it if you keep crying and if i'm being honest here
you'll be the one taking me since i can't swim and all don't cry but that'll be hard because i'm so
happy is there anything that doesn't make you cry well anyway when we go to leave this place
everyone's gonna recognize you aren't they yes that'll be a problem no it won't because i've got
the perfect idea to get you out of here
mermaid princess are you all right look over there at the tower do you see that two skeleton
this is worse than my greatest fear those weren't the sounds of axes or knives like usual
what we heard were the bodies of human pirates slamming against the tower how disgusting that
vanderdecken he's nothing short of a monster
i think we're in trouble i think you're right it appears they all survived but how the ryugu palace is
supposed to be impregnable yet we've been invaded by enemy forces the king the princess everyone here
we're all in danger hey it sounds like it finally stopped you ready scaredy cat sure we're counting on you
megalo
let's go break through
megalo and luffy is with him we're off to the sea forest
luffy escapes with shira hoshi throwing the palace into an even greater panic the pirates who've
infiltrated its walls attack with a strange desperation carrying out a mission that the straw hats have yet
to understand meanwhile after a scuffle of their own sanji and chopper come across an injured haji
on the next one piece the ryugu palace in shock the kidnapping of shira hoshi i'm gonna be king of the pirates